Society of Federal Labor Relations Professionals Publications 5532
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Society of Federal Labor Relations Professionals Publications
1974-1976
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Society of Federal Labor Relations Professionals
5532
0.33 cubic feet
0.3 linear ft.
Records (documents), publications (documents).
Publications of the Society of Federal Labor Relations Professionals.
5659411
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, April 07, 2009
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 18, 2019
Scope and Contents
Includes copies of 1974, 1975, and 1976 convention programs, copy of a paper submitted by Wilson Hart for the 1974 convention, copies of papers submitted at the 1975 convention other than those printed in Public Personnel Management. These include remarks by Fibish, Freehling, Chaskelson, Tobias, Reuben and Black.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Society of Federal Labor Relations Professionals (U.S.)
5659411
- Society of Labor Relations Professionals' Convention Programs, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  February 7-8, 1974. 2 copies.
  - Item 1: Convention '74; The Evolving Federal Labor Relations Program, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By Society of Federal Labor Relations Professionals (SFLRP). February 7-8, 1974. 2 copies. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Convention '75: Problems and Prospects for Federal Labor Relations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By Society of Federal Labor Relations Professionals (SFLRP). February 27-28, 1975. 2 copies. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Convention '76: Federal Labor-Management Relations: Current Problems and Future Solutions, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By Society of Federal Labor Relations Professionals (SFLRP). Febraury 19-20, 1976. 3 copies. Item is in English.
- The Labor Relations Professional in the Federal Sector, 1974; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Labor Relations Professional in the Federal Sector: Role, Expectations, Problems, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By Wilson R. Hart. Remarks prepared for presentation at the SFLRP convention, Feburary 8, 1974. Item is in English.
- Society of Labor Relations Professionals' Convention Proceedings, 1975; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Presentation of Robert M. Tobias to the Society of Labor Relations Professionals' Convention, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By Robert M. Tobias. February 27, 1975. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Problems in Case Presentation and Proof Before Third-Party Agencies: The Federal Service Impasses Panel, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By Ted M. Chaskelson. February 27, 1975. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Introductory Remarks: SLRP Conference, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By Nancy C. Fibish. February 27, 1975. Item is in English.
- Society of Labor Relations Professionals' Convention Proceedings, 1976; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: What the Federal Covernment Can Learn From the State and Local Experience: A Neutral's View, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By Arvid Anderson. Address given at SFLRP convention, February 19, 1976. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Investigation, Prosecution, Decision-Making, Enforcement and Appeals of Unfair Labor Practice Cases, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By Robert J. Canavan. Workshop remarks at SFLRP convention, February 19, 1976. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: 1969 Study Committee Report which led to issuance of E.O. 11491, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By Arthur A. Horowitz. February 19-20, 1976. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: IS There a Demonstrated Need for a Legislated Federal Labor-Management Relations Program?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By Anthony F. Ingrassia. Remarks at SFLRP convention, February 19, 1976. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Impact of EEO and OSHA on Labor Relations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By Erie R. Doyle. Remarks to SFLRP convention, February 20, 1976. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Remarks, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By Seymour Berry. February 20, 1976. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Is There a Demonstrated Need for a Legislated Federal Labor-Management Relations Program?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By Vincent L. Connery. Presented at SFLRP convention, February 19, 1976. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Statutory Appeals Procedures: Status Quo or Change, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By Edward H. Passman. Presented at SFLRP convention, February 19, 1976. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Special Problems in the Establishment of Collective Bargaining Legislation for Federal Employees, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By Maralyn G. Blatch. Speech at SFLRP convention, February 19, 1976. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Effect of the February 1975 Amendments to Executive Order 11491, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By Irving I. Geller. Speech at the SFLRP convention, February 19-20, 1976. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Cutting Costs in Arbitration, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By Frederick U. Reel. Remarks at SFLRP luncheon, June 10, 1976. Item is in English.
- Society of Labor Relations Professionals' Convention Remarks, 1976; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Emerging Importance of Section 10(e), Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Daniel F. Black. Undated remarks from SFLRP convention, February 27, 1975. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Emerging Importance of Section 10(e), Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By S. Jesse Reuben. Undated remarks from SFLRP convention, February 27, 1975. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Problems in Case Presentation and Proof Before Third-Party Agencies, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Robert J. Freehling. Undated remarks from SFLRP convention, February 27, 1975. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Criteria for the Selection of a Wage System, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Robert R. Fredlund. Undated remarks from SFLRP convention, February 20, 1976. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Effect of the February 1975 Amendments to Executive Order 11491, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By James Lyons. Undated remarks from SFLRP convention, February 19, 1976. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Statutory Adverse-Action Appellate System, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Wilma L. Lehman. Undated remarks from SFLRP convention, February 19, 1976. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Impact of the 1975 Amendments to Executive Order 11491 on Labro-Management Relations in VA, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Michael Rudd. Undated remarks from SFLRP convention, February 19, 1976. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Investigation, Prosecution, Decisionmaking, Enforcement and Appeals of Unfair Labor Cases, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Edward T. Borda. Undated remarks from SFLRP convention, February 19, 1976. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Statutory Appeals Procedures: Status Quo or Change?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Seymour Alloy. Undated remarks from SFLRP convention, February 19, 1976. Item is in English.